{
    "lvl3":[
        {
            "question": "Fill in the blank to declare the scanner: Scanner scan = ___ Scanner(System.in)",
            "answer": "new",
            "id": 1   
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of the scanner? Scanner read = new Scanner(System.in)",
            "answer": "read",
            "id": 2   
        },
        {
            "question": "Fill in the blank while having the scanner named scan: String name = ____.nextLine();",
            "answer": "scan",
            "id": 3   
        },
        {
            "question": "Fill in the blank for taking in an int as an input: scan._______();",
            "answer": "nextInt",
            "id": 4   
        },
        {
            "question": "Fill in the blank for taking in a float as an input: scan._________();",
            "answer": "nextFloat",
            "id": 5   
        },
        {
            "question": "Fill in the blank for the import of the scanner class: import java.util._______; ",
            "answer": "Scanner",
            "id": 6   
        },
        {
            "question": "Fill in the blank in order to create a variable string to be taken as an input: ______ sentence = scan.nextLine();",
            "answer": "String",
            "id": 7   
        },
        {
            "question": "Fill in the blank for taking in a string for a scanner named scan: _____________();",
            "answer": "scan.nextLine",
            "id": 8   
        },
        {
            "question": "Fill in the blank for taking in a float for a scanner named scan: ______________();",
            "answer": "scan.nextFloat",
            "id": 9   
        },
        {
            "question": "Fill in the blank to import the scanner class: ______ java.util.Scanner",
            "answer": "import",
            "id": 10   
        }
    ] 
}